Baba, the envelope looks good, friend.
[laughter]
What are you putting in the bag about the envelope?
Envelope
[laughs]
Brother, whether the girl's first kitchen is done or not, it is
Papa's.  [laughter]
I'll be married soon.
[Music]
Wow, he's got something going on.
Bring the black one
too,
no, no, you are
tightening the nut, give me medicine for its
cold, give me
medicine, give me medicine
[laughs] I know it is
right,
you are agree, do a
proper prostration at both the feet
[laughs]
I will touch it myself, tell me about your
husband [laughs] about your
husband, I am
not married yet [laughs] come on come on
[laughter]
now Kivi has said come on what are you saying
Kiwi what are you saying Kivi make me feel
great, make me
feel great,
oh Kivi said something very good
what are you saying Kivi
feel everyone, you said make
everyone feel
Kiwi, you will get married soon.
Yes.  [laughter]
This girl will do it with this girl.   It will happen
with the girl.   So you
won't do it?
What?  [laughter]
What's its name?
Today there is a short clip.
What is his name?
This is beautiful.
Gandhi
Gandhi [laughs]
and I am beautiful.
No.
Today Vihaan made a fortune.
Well, now I am not in the mood for marriage.
[laughs] You wo
n't get it, you wo
n't get it [laughs]
You won't get food, you
need food [laughs] He was
teaching me wrong things, that's why I stopped eating. Do you
know what happened on the wedding day,
I came all ready, I
opened the gate and left it. When I saw you looking so dirty,
I got scared.
I was joking [laughs] Is
she looking good or dirty?   Is it the
same thing brother, that girl will not change, out of all these,
who looks good among
all these ladies,
yours [laughs]
[laughs] take it
and ask them,
now there are two dirty ladies, then it is a pair, okay
[laughs]
okay, tell her like this once, hey, get
married to your younger brother, get
married
[laughs] okay then do it
[laughs]
okay
my clip got cut
[laughter] here you go, you will get beaten
every day, you will get beaten
[laughter] she said
dirty things to me, she
said dirty things to me, you will get beaten [laughs]
sorry, sorry, after today,
Sitaram Bhojanale's fame [laughs] has reached
this level.  Earlier,
people used to come from 1.5 km away to eat.  These
days I spend two to two hours preparing the dish from the range of ₹100
and have been waiting for the last three quarters of an hour for the
dish prepared by Papa.
Daddy, what is it that you like about your taste buds
?  Just look.
I will tell you after eating it.
Yesterday I asked Papa randomly.  I said,
Papa, how are you feeling?  Are people coming from far away
?  Children are saying that this is God's
grace.  [laughs]
Mom and Dad had a fight about this today.
Today Papa made chole with his recipe and
added some of his ingredients.  So mom is saying that
this cannot be put in it.   I did
not add cardamom and cloves.
In today's one, I have
added some items which mom is saying cannot be added.
So she is saying, don't teach me.
[laughs] I said in your dish, not till today, right
?
So should we dare to eat or not?   Ca
n't eat.  The experiments were good.  The
first meals are
not very good.  Very good.   Did
not eat chickpeas.  I said we will
take the risk together.  [laughs] If
something ever happens to me after eating alone,
because
brother, it may or may not have been a girl's first kitchen.   It's done for
dad.  [laughter]
Tell me, I am telling you.  First kitchen mom.
Yes.  [laughter] We haven't had our first girl's kitchen yet.
Why are you
scared poor guy, no no no there is nothing to be
scared of.
What is there to be afraid of?   There is nothing to
fear.
We know.
Nothing [laughs] will
happen like that, friend.
Priya Priya
Priya cooks very lovely food.
Makes it.
Yes
no, it genuinely makes good.
Yes.  She makes it very well.   I
add less spices than my father.
Once you just make it,
Papa, add some of our spicy spices.  I do
n't eat spicy food.  Same thing happened yesterday too, you know, there were two
types of kidney beans yesterday.  First Papa got his
test done then Mummy told her Papa [laughs]
Mummy said Papa has passed.
Both of them passed.  [laughter]
Now she's sitting on the opposite side of Mommy's hand.   I ca
n't say it, mom, she has become my sister.  [laughter] I did it.
Well, the
normal spice guys were doing it.  You will have to do both.
No, dad, [laughs]
mom's is also very good.
Jasleen did this to show that
more questions were asked about mother.  Mom, please give me yours.
[laughter]
You also had retakes.  Mummy's?   I had
bought Papa's.  Mummy's tight.  You
asked which ones mom had made.
Look, this is my toy.  From today
I have given this toy to this girl.  Take
care of my toy.  Don't leave it hungry,
don't leave it alone.
Ok.  I would leave it.   I
will leave it.  [laughter]
Will I leave it?   It
gives the opposite.
Tell me how soon will we both get married?
Hey, just one question.
Look what she is saying about both of us.  Please
scold him once.  Why are you not getting married
?  Just ask.   I am
sorry, I will do it
tomorrow.
What is it waiting for?   Of
Kiwi growing up.
Ask me what [laughs] thing are you waiting for brother?
Wait for what?
Write down the weight.
Write the date.  Write the date.   I will
write down the date.  What date should I write?
When is your birthday?   Of
Sunday.   Of
Sunday.
Sunday is coming [laughs].
Tension.
Tangent.   It
comes right.  I will do it only then.  Tension.  Okay, fine
brother.
Ok.
What day does it come?
What day does yours come?
Mine is April 17th.
Okay, you asked me.  [laughs]
First, tell me, will you take care of the toy I gave you?
When does Goku come?   Come
quickly.  Papa, you also come.
Today uncle will taste the chole made by father.
Put the chole first, friend.  Papa is waiting.   Let me
add the chickpeas.
[laughter]
Come on, brother.
Papa, you also sit with me.  Uncle will
take the risk alone.
No, they are tasty ones.   It's
great.   I have already
told you the face.   It's
great.
Kiwi, will you eat these chole?
My dad made these.
Hey, just tell me how it is made.  [laughs]
No, no, they're well made.  Excellent.   They are
well made.  They are well made.  Brother, I will
also serve Papa's plate.  Yes,
who will lick it?   Please
give one spoon to uncle also.
Come try Papa's Chole once.   Come.
Hum Aapki Last Wala Episode.
Hey, I will not make a corpse in this.
Hey man, you guys are playing my CID
episode.   I have
applied it.  Where is it in this?
Hey [laughter]
come come come.   Let
me show you.  Come sit.
[MUSIC]
Great.
Excellent.   It's a
matter of honesty.
Excellent.
How did you make it?
Sure Uncle.
Uncle is already eating.
I am already eating.
Uncle is just eating chole.
Eating chickpeas.  Eating chickpeas.
Look at it brother.  My father doesn't just show it like that.
Papa's taste is very strong.
[laughter]
Now we are calling people from outside and
giving you proof.
Brother, did you really like brother-in-law?
Yes.  Right now this is the first brother.
No, I would have told you about the test in advance
brother.   The one
that
is served with chole kulcha,
yes, they are served like that with peas, I don't know what they
call it.
Looks great.   Isn't it
great?   They are
good.
Shaur Papa, this recipe of yours too.
Today, Papa and Mummy had a real
fight.
Tea leaf water is added to it.
Boil tea leaves in water for colour.  That's a different
recipe.  Mom never used it.  There would be a
fight between mom and dad that friend
what are you putting in this, dad would say
stop the tune I am cooking it, what do you want, what do you want
kiwi, what are you getting put
in the bag
dad [laughs]
put it in my bag,
bring it, I will keep it or
not, there is no sharing in this, there is
trust, it is
yours only, trust is the most in
kiwi, do one thing listen you trust me, right,
you can give me your envelope, no no, I
refused myself,
kiwi, ok check it, sit down Bhabhi,
I have kept it once, oh
I have already had so many sarees,
no, this time you wear the shirt [laughs]
I can use it as a blouse,
we have a shirt for you too, wear it
[laughs]
see last time I had taken it because of your saying,
oh baba the envelope is not looking good.
Give it to me [laughs].   They are
saying remove the envelope.   Give it
to G also.  [laughter]
Oh, Daddy, you should
give the photo to Khindi ji also.  [laughs]
Okay,
take this one too [laughs] while taking it like this, come let me
take a photo of you with your envelope.  Kiwi
Kiwi
Kiwi Take a photo of you with your envelope.
Yes, yes,
Kiwi bag has become very expensive.
Bellavi
has three.  [laughter]
He has the Count.
You have two in this.  Two.  Where did three come from?   There are
two.   There
are three.
Whose three are these?
In this, children's counting does not get affected.
Tell me who it is.   Come here.
Fix the bag.  Come here.
Yes, okay.
What?
Look, she has fallen ill.   She has fallen
ill.  She is not eating food.  Hey,
what did you remember?
[laughter] These are the ones who go
out most of the time I rarely go out
well
she should also get one by the way the
bigger one
[sound of clearing throat]
that's what I knew she would say something [laughter]
you had recorded it
what to do what to do
kiwi is saying put all those envelopes whatever you have
in my bag
I will keep the
bread don't go
but kiwi how much do you think about me
then will you give me this bag
how many are there behind this now
two pieces of fruit in your bag also that's
five
total that is that [laughter] come on hey hey
kept this hey mommy didn't keep
this in your bag
[laughter]
yes bhabhi come here hey hey don't
pluck the flower just yet wait
[laughter] let me give you the
gift first pick
this one pick it up
whom are you talking uncle wo
n't get up you won't get up
son I kept your bag behind actually she is
talking about this bag the
pink one
yes it is the pink one that is your bag so
this is my bag my school
tuition bag my
tuition bag is in
it  What is?
What's in it?
What's in it?  What's in it?
What is something?  What?
Okay, I will give it to you, first tell me what is in it?
Wait, wait, I know.  Here's your bag.
What's in it, Kiwi?
No, just tell me like this.  Don't open it.  Tell me
what is there in it?
What else was there?
Envelope.  [laughter]
What's in the envelope?   By
opening it.   Do
n't open it.  [laughter] Come on, sit, sit,
I'll sit, is it
coming in the back, open the top like that,
brother Priya [sound of clearing throat]
[sound of coughing]
so good to see [laughter]
you're very happy right now you're looking a
little cuter [laughter] you
look very happy I'm
not saying too much, friend, nothing else, no,
I'm getting emotional, too much
happiness, if I wait any
longer my happiness will be gone
[laughter]
come on Priya, go meet daddy quickly don't move the
seat back like this, you have to move the
seat back, did you get
your number,
son, son, no, saree babu, I ca
n't find the
saree like this, the
photo is at the back, come back, hands inside,
out of front
[nasal noise]
come on, move it forward, I'll sit from there and move your seat
forward, straighten your seat a little,
sit from there,
Priya, wow, you got in the car and this one is covered, the one in front of
us keeps turning around
[laughter] I said
anything, come on, it will
defame the poor
Kiwi, poor Kiwi has kept her pink
bag next to her [laughter]
Okay uncle, bye bye bye
[laughs] should I tell you
one thing, should I tell you a secret, I took
out the envelopes from your bag, but you
said don't take them out [laughs]
Kiwi, where is your envelope,
where is your envelope,
okay bye bye bye Sharda ji, bye
okay ji, bye
Sajal, take care, drive slowly brother, bye bye
-b
water has fallen on the tyres,
whenever a girl leaves the house, they
throw water on the tyres.
Finally
Papa's chole got praised.  Daddy
looks happy today.
What happened to you?
Now our ball is about to turn sour.
You stay away from it.
I will try to stay away from it.
You are the younger sister.
Hey, don't you give him all this that we have?
Just take this and keep it.  What to do?
No, what to do?  What if
I just drop them home and
I am also very tired, friend.  Then I will come and
sleep.  Let's.  [music]